Guide to the George Matsumoto Papers
George Matsumoto Papers
1945-1991
1945 1991
Matsumoto George 1922-
MC 00042
The bulk of these papers and drawings document the architectural practice of George Matsumoto between 1948 and 1961. The collection includes correspondence, photographs, blueprints, scrapbooks, and architectural drawings that pertain to his modern residential and commercial designs.
Architect George Matsumoto served on the faculty of the School of Design of North Carolina State College of Agriculture and Engineering (later North Carolina State University) from 1948 to 1961. During his tenure at the School of Design, Matsumoto won more than thirty awards for his residential work and his achievements in design were widely published
12.5 linear feet
North Carolina State University Libraries, Special Collections Research Center
Gift of George Matsumoto, 1996 June 6; 1997 July 23.
The collection is divided into five series. The first of these series is the Correspondence series, which provides information on Matsumoto's relationship with his clients and the larger triangular relationship of the architect, client, and builder. Photographs by architectural photographer Joseph Molitor document completed projects and were used by Matsumoto for publications of his own projects. Tear sheets and photographs for most of Matsumoto's North Carolina projects comprise the second series, the Publications and Photographs Series. The third series includes Mounted Photographs used for presentations. The fourth series, Reduced Blueprints is a small sample of major commercial projects completed in California by the firm between 1964 and 1991, including the Bechtel Engineering Center at the University of California at Berkeley. Finally, the bulk of the collection lies in the Drawings and Sketches series, which includes much of his North Carolina work.
July 16, 1922 Born, San Francisco, California
1943 Earned B.A., Architecture, Washington University, Saint Louis, Missouri
1945 Earned M.A. with honors, Cranbrook Academy of Art, Bloomfield Hills, Michigan; studied under Eliel Saarinen
1945-1946 Senior Designer, Skidmore, Owings and Merrill, Chicago, Illinois
1946-1947 Senior Planner-Designer, Saarinen and Swanson, Birmingham, Michigan
1947-1948 Principal, Runnells, Clark, Waugh, and Matsumoto, Kansas City, Missouri
1948-1961 School of Design, North Carolina State College of Agriculture and Engineering
1948-1951 Assistant Professor of Architecture
1951-1957 Associate Professor of Architecture
1957-1961 Professor of Architecture
1961-1967 Professor, College of Environmental Design, University of California, Berkeley
1961-1969 Principal, George Matsumoto and Associates, San Francisco, California
1969-1970 Principal, J. Francis Ward and George Matsumoto, San Francisco, California
1970-1991 Principal, George Matsumoto and Associates, San Francisco, California
North Carolina Buildings Collection, MC 00225
Architectural Models of Buildings Designed by George Matsumoto, MC 00447
North Carolina Buildings Collection, MC 00225
Architectural Models of Buildings Designed by George Matsumoto, MC 00447
The bulk of these papers and drawings document the architectural practice of George Matsumoto and Associates between 1948 and 1961. These years correspond to his residence in Raleigh, North Carolina, and his tenure on the faculty of North Carolina State College (later North Carolina State University). The collection relates solely to Matsumoto's architectural practice, and there is limited information regarding Matsumoto's personal life and teaching career. Projects in the collection include residential work chiefly in Raleigh, but also in Chapel Hill, Sedgefield (Greensboro), and Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina, and Richmond, Virginia. Formats include correspondence, publications, scrapbooks, photographs, architectural drawings, blueprints, specifications, and sketches.
Matsumoto George 1922-; Matsumoto George 1922-; George Matsumoto and Associates; North Carolina State University School of Design; Drawings; Blueprints; Photographs; Buildings, structures, etc. San Francisco (Calif.); Architecture; Letters (correspondence); Raleigh (N.C.) Buildings, structures, etc.; North Carolina Architects; Architecture History United States 20th century; North Carolina 20th century Architectural drawing; North Carolina 20th century Architectural practice
- Correspondence, 1948-1968; 1948 1968; 1.25 linear feet
  Correspondence includes letters, contracts, invoices, statements, sketches, and other materials that document the professional relationship between Matsumoto, his client, and the builder on the project. The content of this material ranges from routine exchanges to in-depth discussions regarding the design process and client needs. The projects in this series are chiefly residential, however, several unbuilt commercial projects are represented. The series is arranged chronologically by client.
  - Matsumoto Residence, 1952-1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Matsumoto Residence, 1953-1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Kelly, Walter J., 1952 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Kelly, Walter J., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Kelly, Walter J., 1954 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Kelly, Walter J., 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Kelly, Walter J.: Statements and Contracts, 1952-1955 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Kelly, Walter J.: Specifications, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Taylor, Isaac, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Julian, Milton, 1953-1956 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Aretakis, Gus, 1953-1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Johnson Company, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Johnson Company, 1955-1960 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Poland, George, 1954-1956 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Poole Equipment Company, 1954-1959 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Woodward, H., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Hicks, Thomas, 1955-1966 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Lipman, Eric M., 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Lipman, Eric M., 1956 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Lipman, Eric M., 1957 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Lipman, Eric M., 1957-1963 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Kaplan, Marcus, 1956-1960 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - North Carolina State College Fraternity Houses, 1956-1964 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Woman's Day Project, 1948, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Woman's Day Project, 1958-1964 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Hudson, Gwen, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Hudson, Gwen, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Jeffrey's Equipment Company, 1959-1964 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - DeWitt, B. S., 1959-1964 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Thrower, Edwin K., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Thrower, Edwin K., 1960-1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Tate, A. R., 1961-1967 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Watkins, William, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Moore, Frank, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Leiderman, P. H., 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Martin, M. J., 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Projects and Inquiries, 1955-1962 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Publications and Photographs, 1950-1984 (bulk 1950-1968); 1.75 linear feet
  The majority of this series contains tear sheets form various publications, chiefly from Pencil Point magazine, of the bulk of Matsumoto's North Carolina and Virginia residential work. It includes photographs taken by Joseph Molitor and used by Matsumoto to enhance the presentation of publications and articles on his projects. Generally the photographs in the series have been cut up or altered to match the relevant published photographs. The series is arranged chronologically by project.
  - Richter Residence, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Julian Residence, 1953-1956 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Poole Equipment Company, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Poole Residence, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Poole Lake House, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Johnson Company House, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - North Carolina State College, School of Design Addition, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Matsumoto Residence, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Poland Residence, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Adams Residence, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Woman's Day Vacation House/Douglas Fir Plywood Association, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Lipman Residence, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Westinghouse House Project, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Thrower Residence at Sedgefield, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Blumeyer Apartments, St. Louis, Missouri, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Park Shore Housing, Brooklyn, New York, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - City Gate West, Chicago, Illinois, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Family Housing at the Presidio of San Francisco, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - School of Nursing, University of California at San Francisco, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Bechtel Engineering Center, University of California at Berkeley, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - City of Santa Clara, Parks and Recreation, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Model of Unidentified Residence, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - San Domenico School for Girls Library, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Publications, miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Interview, March 30, 1996, 1996 1996 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Blueprint negatives (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook, 1945-1958 (Flatbox 7, Volume 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1959-1964 (Flatbox 7, Volume 2)
- Mounted Photographs, undated; 0.5 linear feet
  This series contains black and white photographs from selected Matsumoto projects mounted on 12 x 15 presentation boards for use in lectures and presentations. All photographs in this series were taken by Joseph Molitor, a prominent architectural photographer. Series is arranged chronologically by project.
  - Richter Residence, Raleigh, North Carolina (Oversizeflatbox 8)
  - Julian Residence, Chapel Hill, North Carolina (Oversizeflatbox 8)
  - Poole Lake House, Raleigh, North Carolina (Oversizeflatbox 8)
  - Poole Equipment Company, Raleigh, North Carolina (Oversizeflatbox 8)
- Reduced Blueprints, 1966-1991; 1966 1991; 0.5 linear feet
  Series includes a sample of four major projects from the firm of George Matsumoto and Associates between 1964 and 1991. These commercial works represent the major projects from Matsumoto's practice in California. Series is arranged chronologically by project.
  - Design Folio, Department of Defense, Family Housing, 1964 (Oversizebox 9, Folder 1)
  - Design Folio, Presidio of San Francisco, California, 150 Units Family Housing, 1966-1968 (Oversizebox 9, Folder 2)
  - Multiple Crafts Shop Addition, Presidio of San Francisco, 1973 (Oversizebox 9, Folder 3)
  - School of Nursing Building, UC-San Francisco Medical Center, 1968 (Oversizebox 9, Folder 4)
  - Bechtel Engineering Center, UC-Berkeley, College of Engineering, 1978 (Oversizebox 9, Folder 5)
  - East Oakland Senior Center and Library, Oakland, California, 1991 (Oversizebox 9, Folder 6)
- Drawings and Sketches, 1947-1991
  The bulk of the collection is represented by this group of drawings. Chiefly North Carolina projects, the drawings represent Matsumoto's award-winning residential work. Several unbuilt projects are represented and generally preliminary studies as well as completed working drawings are present. There are a limited number of design sketches and renderings, however several preliminary plans and studies with each project reflect the considerable time Matsumoto spent working closely with his clients. Series is arranged chronologically by project.
  - Kamphoefner Residence, 3 Conceptual Sketches, 1949
    - 30 x 12 ink on tracing paper (Flatfolder 10)
    - 18 x 12 ink on tracing paper (Flatfolder 10)
    - 18 x 12 blueprint (Flatfolder 10)
  - Nesselrode Doctor's Clinic, Kansas City, Missouri, 1947
    - Working drawings, 36 x 24, 11 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 11)
  - Ritcher Residence, Raleigh, North Carolina, 1950
    - Working drawings, 36 x 24, 11 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 12)
  - Poole Lake House, Raleigh, North Carolina, 1950
    - Working drawings, 36 x 24, 7 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 12)
  - Jackson Residence, Raleigh, North Carolina, 1951
    - Preliminary drawings, 36 x 24, 5 sheets, pencil on tracing paper, marked void (Flatfolder 12)
  - Matsumoto Residence, Raleigh, North Carolina, 1952
    - Working drawings, 24 x 18, 14 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 13)
  - Kelly Residence, Southern Pines, North Carolina, 1952
    - Preliminary drawings, 36 x 26, 3 sheets, pencil on tracing paper, marked void (Flatfolder 14)
    - Preliminary drawings, 29 x 23, 2 sheets, blueprints with pencil mark up (Flatfolder 14)
  - Taylor Residence Project, Chapel Hill, North Carolina, 1952
    - Preliminary drawings, 32 x 21, 3 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 15)
    - Preliminary drawings, 32 x 21, 2 sheets, blueprints (Flatfolder 15)
    - Preliminary drawings, 36 x 24, 1 sheet, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 15)
    - Preliminary drawings, 37 x 25, 2 sheets, pencil on linen (Flatfolder 15)
  - Julian Residence, Chapel Hill, North Carolina, 1952-1956
    - Preliminary drawings, 26 x 16, 5 sheets, blueprint with crayon markup (Flatfolder 16)
    - Preliminary drawings, 28 x 17, 4 sheets, pencil and ink on tracing paper (Flatfolder 16)
    - Preliminary rendering, 30 x 20, 1 sheet, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 16)
    - Working drawings, 36 x 24, 8 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 16)
    - Car port drawing, 25 x 23, 1 sheet, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 16)
    - Plywood cabinet, 25 x 23, 1 sheet, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 16)
    - Basement enclosure, 37 x 24, 1 sheet, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 16)
  - Aretakis Residence, Raleigh, North Carolina, 1953
    - Working drawings, 36 x 24, 9 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 17)
  - Johnson Company House, Oak Park, Illinois, 1953-1954
    - Preliminary sketches, 30 x 18, 17 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 18)
    - Preliminary sketches, 36 x 24, 1 sheet, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 18)
    - Working drawings, 37 x 25, 24 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 18)
    - Working drawing, 37 x 25, 1 sheet, blueprint (Flatfolder 18)
  - Demonstration House for the General Electric Company, 1953
    - Working drawings, 36 x 24, 8 sheets, pencil on tracing paper and linen (Flatfolder 19)
  - Poland Residence, Raleigh, North Carolina, 1954
    - Preliminary drawings, 16 x 20, 9 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 20)
    - Working drawings, 36 x 24, 10 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 20)
  - Lipman Residence, Richmond, Virginia, 1955-1957
    - Final breakdown of costs and one letter, 36 x 10, 5 sheets, typescript (Flatfolder 21)
    - Specifications, 36 x 10, 4 sheets, typescript (Flatfolder 21)
    - Preliminary drawings and revisions, 36 x 24, 11 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 21)
    - Working drawings, 36 x 24, 15 sheets, pencil on tracing paper and 2 blueprints (Flatfolder 21)
  - Hicks Residence, Rocky Mount, North Carolina, 1955; 1958
    - Preliminary drawings, 25 x 18, 7 sheets, pencil on linen (Flatfolder 22)
    - Preliminary drawings, 36 x 24, 5 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 22)
    - Design sketch, 24 x 17, 1 sheet, ink on tracing paper (Flatfolder 22)
    - Working drawings, 36 x 24, 12 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 22)
    - Built-in cabinet addition, 36 x 18, 1 sheet, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 22)
  - Poole Residence, Raleigh, North Carolina, 1956
    - Preliminary drawings and studies, 36 x 24, 9 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 23)
    - Preliminary drawings and studies, 36 x 24, 1 blueprint with notations (Flatfolder 23)
  - Paschal Studio Addition, Durham, North Carolina, 1957
    - Working drawings, 36 x 24, 3 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 23)
  - Office/Warehouse - Virginia Cigarette Service, Roanoke, Virginia, 1956-1959
    - Preliminary and Working Drawings, 36 x 24, 13 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 24)
  - 2 and 3 Bedroom Homes for Woman's Day Magazine, 1957-1959
    - Preliminary Drawings and Perspectives, 24 x 18, 10 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 25)
  - Community Church of Chapel Hill, Chapel Hill, North Carolina, 1957
    - [Cecil D. Elliot, Associate] (Flatfolder 26)
    - Preliminary plans and perspectives, 31 x 21, 16 sheets, blueprint (Flatfolder 26)
    - Plot plan, 31 x 19, 1 sheet, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 26)
    - Working drawings, 36 x 24, 14 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 26)
  - Radio Station WCBT and Transmitter, Roanoke Rapids, 1957
    - Preliminary Plans, 36 x 24, 10 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 27)
  - Adams Residence, Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina, 1957-1965
    - Sketches, preliminary plans, additions, various sizes, 21 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 28)
    - Working drawings, 36 x 24, 17 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 28)
    - Revisions, 36 x 24, 3 sheets, blueprints (Flatfolder 28)
  - Residence for Cecile and Bryce DeWitt, Chapel Hill, North Carolina, 1958
    - Sketches, preliminary drawings, various sizes, 12 sheets, pencil and ink on tracing paper (Flatfolder 29)
    - Working Drawings, 36 x 24, 14 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 29)
  - Hudson Residence, Richmond, Virginia, 1958-1959
    - Preliminary plans, 26 x 19, 3 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 30)
    - Working drawings, 36 x 20, 14 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 30)
  - Office Building for Pitt Medical Associates, Greenville, North Carolina, 1958-1960
    - Preliminary plans, 36 x 24, 18 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 31)
    - Working drawings, 36 x 24, 21 sheets, pencil and ink on tracing paper (Flatfolder 31)
  - Vacation House for Woman's Day - Douglas Fir Plywood Association, 1958
    - Preliminary plans and sketches, 36 x 32, 5 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 32)
  - Bellefonte Country Club Addition, Ashland, Kentucky, 1958
    - Perspectives and Plans, 36 x 16, 9 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 33)
  - Jack Rowland Beach Cottage, Atlantic Beach, North Carolina, 1958
    - Preliminary Plans, 36 x 24, 4 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 34)
  - North Florida Junior College, Madison County, Florida, 1958-1959
    - Site Plans, 36 x 24, 7 sheets, blueprints with notations (Flatfolder 35)
  - Wohlman Studio Apartments, 1959
    - Preliminary plans, 36 x 24, 2 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 36)
  - Westinghouse Total Electric Houses, 1959
    - Preliminary Plans, 36 x 24, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 37)
    - Florida Area, 7 sheets (Flatfolder 37)
    - Little Rock, Arkansas, 8 sheets (Flatfolder 37)
    - Jackson, Mississippi, 8 sheets (Flatfolder 37)
    - Atlanta, Georgia, 8 sheets (Flatfolder 37)
  - Thrower Residence I, Sedgefield, North Carolina, 1959-1960
    - Lot Plan, Sedgefield development, 2 sheets, blueprints (Flatfolder 38)
    - Conceptual sketches, various sizes, 11 sheets, ink on tracing paper (Flatfolder 38)
    - Prelim. plans and revisions, 36 x 24, 15 sheets, pencil on tracing paper and blueprints (Flatfolder 38)
    - Working drawings, 36 x 24, 17 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 38)
  - Thrower Residence II, Greensboro, North Carolina, 1974-1975
    - Preliminary plans, 36 x 24, 29 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 39)
  - Thrower Residence III, Key Largo, Florida, 1981
    - Preliminary plans, 34 x 23, 8 sheets, blueprints (Flatfolder 40)
    - Revisions, 34 x 23, 1 sheet, ink on paper (Flatfolder 40)
  - North Carolina State College Fraternity Houses
    - Pi Kappa Alpha and Sigma Phi Epsilon, 1960-1961 (Flatfolder 41)
    - Preliminary plans, 23 x 17, 17 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 41)
    - Preliminary plans, 36 x 24, 11 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 41)
    - Details, Alcoa Extrusions, 36 x 24, 8 sheets, ink on tracing paper (Flatfolder 41)
  - IBM Building, Winston-Salem, North Carolina, 1960
    - Rendering, 18 x 12, 1 sheet, photostatic copy (Flatfolder 42)
    - Sketches, 36 x 14, 2 sheets, ink on tissue paper (Flatfolder 42)
    - Preliminary drawings, 36 x 24, 10 sheets, blueprints and pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 42)
  - IBM Building, Winston-Salem, North Carolina, 1960
    - Working drawings, 36 x 24, 28 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 43)
  - Tate Residence, Winston-Salem, North Carolina, 1961
    - Preliminary drawings, 36 x 24, 3 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 44)
  - Residence for Frank Moore, Raleigh, North Carolina, 1961
    - Working drawings, 36 x 24, 15 sheets, pencil on tracing paper and blueprints (Flatfolder 45)
  - Vacation Cabin for Masonite Corporation and Woman's Day Magazine, Cape Code, Massachusetts, 1961
    - Sketch and Preliminary drawings, 36 x 24, 9 sheets, pencil on tracing paper and blueprints (Flatfolder 46)
  - Watkins Residence, Raleigh, North Carolina, 1962
    - Preliminary drawings, 25 x 18, 9 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 47)
    - Preliminary drawings, 36 x 24, 2 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 47)
    - Working drawings, 36 x 24, 20 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 47)
  - Branch Office Building, IBM Corporation, Raleigh, North Carolina, 1963
    - Conceptual sketches, 32 x 18, 8 sheets, black crayon on tissue paper (Flatfolder 48)
  - Branch Office Building, IBM Corporation, Raleigh, North Carolina, 1963
    - Preliminary schemes and drawings, 36 x 24, 21 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 49)
    - Site plan, topographic maps, 36 x 24, 5 sheets, blueprints (Flatfolder 50)
    - Working drawings, 36 x 24, 38 sheets, pencil on tracing paper architectural, structural, mechanical, and electrical (Flatfolder 51)
  - U.S. Department of Defense, Military Housing, 1963
    - Preliminary Study, 36 x 24, 41 sheets, pencil on tracing paper and blueprints (Flatfolder 52)
  - Park Shore Development, Brooklyn, New York, 1963-1964
    - Preliminary studies, 36 x 24, 18 sheets, pencil on tracing paper, 2 blueprints (Flatfolder 53)
  - Park Shore Development Housing, Brooklyn, New York, 1965
    - Misc. sketches and studies, various sizes, 78 sheets, pencil on tracing paper (Flatfolder 54)
  - City Gate West, Chicago, Illinois, 1968
    - Misc. presentation posters, var. sizes, 16 sheets, blueprints, photostats, and negatives (Flatfolder 55)
    - Project flowchart, 2 sheets, blueprints
- Architectural Model
  - Architectural Model of the George Matsumoto Home in Raleigh, 1958 (Oversizebox 56)